(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T17:51:51.383418",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
重ねた手は ぎゅっと離さずに
Without letting go of our intertwined hands,
行くよ 夢見る空へ
let's go to the sky where dreams await.
はあちゃまちまー！
Haachamachama!
窓格子に見上げた とてもの小さな空
Looking up through the window at the tiny, tiny sky,
ここで出会えたのは 数えきれない奇跡
meeting here is a countless miracle.
繰り返す日常が
Our repeating daily lives
きらめきを繋いで
connect sparkles,
星のような笑顔導いた
guiding smiles like stars.
Day by Day みんなの越えた時間が
Day by day, the time we've overcome together,
Face to Face ここでぞろぞろ目覚めるもの
face to face, awakening one after another here—
ぞろぞろ描くもの ざりざり描いた夢へ
drawing one by one, towards the dreams we sketched.
重ねた手は ぎゅっと離さずに
Without letting go of our intertwined hands,
瞳に映る 描き出すときめき
the excitement reflected in our eyes comes alive.
振り向くことなく真っ直ぐに
Moving straight ahead without looking back,
行くよ 夢見る空へ
let's go to the sky where dreams await.
笑い合ったことや 突き刺さる痛い思い出いっぱいなのに
Even with all the shared laughs and piercing painful memories,
あっという間の日々 裏表じゃなくて
time flies by in the blink of an eye, not two-faced,
名前つけて保存 どれも重宝したい宝物
giving names and saving them, treasures I want to cherish.
One for All みんなのためが力になる
One for all, everyone's sake becomes my strength,
All for One 共に日向ガス吸いすぎるくらい
All for one, basking together in the sunlight so much
笑顔がもっと笑わない 思いは膨らんでゆく
that our smiles won't stop and our feelings keep growing.
重ねた今をぎゅっと噛みしめた
Savoring this accumulated present tightly,
一人違う 描き出すときめき
each of us bringing a unique, exciting vision to life.
風を感じたら まっすぐに行くよ
Feeling the breeze, we will go straight ahead
夢見る空へ
to the sky where dreams await.
憧れて伸ばし つかみ取ったその光が いつまでも光り続ける
That light we reached out for and grasped will keep shining forever.
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Holding our intertwined hands tightly without letting go,
行くよ！
Let's go!
行こう！
夢見る空へ
To the sky of our dreams!
繋げようよ
Let's connect them!
day by day
みんなの声が力になる
everyone's voice becomes my strength.
stage by stage
ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
what each of us aims for here,
それぞれ描くもの
what each of us draws,
それぞれ願った夢へ
toward the dream each of us wished for.
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Holding our intertwined hands tightly without letting go,
ひとり (ひとり) 違う (色で)
Each with a different color,
描き出すトキメキ
drawing out our excitement.
出会った全てにありがとうを
Saying thank you to everything we've encountered,
奇跡 (起して)
making a miracle happen,
ずっと (側にいるよ 行くよ)
always staying by your side, let's go,
夢見る空へ
to the sky of our dreams!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はーちゃま、はーちゃまー！
Haachama, Haachama!
ワールドワイドな最強アイドル！はーちゃまこと赤井はあとです！
The worldwide strongest idol! I'm Haachama, Akai Haato!
ということで、今日はね、最強アイドルになるべく
And so, today, to become the ultimate idol,
三つのね、試練をやっていこうと思います。
I plan to take on three different trials.
そしてね、1年、何年かぶりの、
And also, for the first time in... how many years,
AS…いや、配信！みんな今日は来てくれてありがとう！最後まで楽しんでってね！
AS... I mean, stream! Thank you everyone for coming today! Enjoy yourselves until the end!
え、実はなんとですね、あの今日の放送
Well, actually, you see... today's broadcast,
え、そして今ね歌っていた夢見る空へ、え、なんと、ま、みんなね聞いて驚くと思うんだけども、電流を流しながら歌っていました！
And the song I was just singing, "Yumemiru Sora e"... surprise! I was singing it while running electric currents through me!
はい！なんとね、もうすでに死ねば始まっているっていうね、驚きのあの電流アイドルみたいな感じなんですけれどもね
Yes! That's right, it's already started before you knew it—sort of like a shocking electric shock idol!
あの今年の、はーちゃまの意図は、あ、もしやね、電流アイドルになるのではないかと、ま、思ってるんだけどさ
And my intention for Haachama this year is... could it be that I'm becoming an electric shock idol? That's what I'm thinking.
ま、そんな感じでね、え、このね電流の説明をすると、あの今ねレベル5、レベル5で電流を流しています。今もねちょうど流れています。
So anyway, to explain this electricity: right now, it's running at level 5. It's actually running right now as we speak.
そしてね、え、自分の歌声と音に合わせて、電流が、電流の強さが変わっていくという感じで、ま、サビになってね、だんだんだんだん、あの電流のレベルが変わっていくっていう、そういう仕様になっておりまーす！
And depending on my singing voice and the music, the strength of the current changes. When the chorus hits, it gradually increases in level—that's how it's designed!
はーい！そしてね、まあ、はーちゃまはさ、最強アイドルだからさ、レベル5くらいの電流で悶絶するわけがないでしょ？
Right! And well, Haachama is the strongest idol, so there's no way I'd be writhing in agony from just a level 5 current, right?
ま、やっぱりね、次の曲も用意しているんだけれども、次の電流レベルはマックスで行こうかと思うんだけど、みんな？
Well, of course, I have the next song ready too, and I thought about going with MAX level current for the next one, but what do you guys think?
え？え？なんかちょっと運営さんから、なんかマックスは止めましょうみたいな
Eh? Eh? The management seems to be telling me, "Let's stop at max" or something.
いやいやいや、はーちゃまならできるって、みんなどう思う？ねえ？はーちゃま電流マックスいけるよね？
No no no, Haachama can totally do it! What do you guys think? Right? Haachama can handle max electricity, right?
あ、え、このなんか、電流が、あの、なんかインターバルレベルがマックスの間をとって10なんだって、レベルが。てことはマックスがレベル20と。まあね、今回ねちょっとね運営さんもなんかすごい心配してるんで
Ah, wait, this current interval level is... taking the middle between max and... it's 10, meaning max is level 20. Well, management is really worried about this,
レベル、ま、さっきまでファイブで、ま、余裕だったんで、次はねレベルをうつーじにしてくれ！次はね、さすがに電流は、
so since level 5 was easy until now, for the next one let's make the level... wait, for the next one...
いやでも今もね喋ってる最中流れてんだよね。そう、レベル5だから、ま、次はねレベル10で、え、早速ね歌っていこうと思います、ちょっと。
Wait, it's actually running right now while I'm talking. So level 5 was fine, next is level 10, and I'll sing right away.
はい！電流2021で、はーちゃま初配信！電流アイドルとして頑張っていこうと思います！
Yes! For "Denryu 2021", Haachama's first stream! I'll do my best as an electric shock idol!
そしてね、コメントもスーパーチャットもみんなありがとう！痛くないよ！全然痛くないの！あのなんかすごいプルプルプルプルね
And thank you everyone for the comments and super chats! It doesn't hurt! It doesn't hurt at all! It's just a lot of shivering...
ではこれから、次の歌をレベル10ので、あの電流で歌っていこうと思いまーす！オッケー！いく、いくからね！
So from here on, I'll sing the next song at level 10 current! Okay! Here we go!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make the newborn excitement ring out!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と 輝きにのって
Ride the brilliance with the best time and the best friends!
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
手の中に つかみたいんだ キラメキライダー☆ 最高だね
I want to grasp it in my hands, Kirameki Rider☆ Isn't it the best?
踏み出せるかな 最初の歌
Will I be able to take that step? My very first song,
私の声が 震えていた
My voice was trembling.
あの日から続く 未来は みんなとつかんだ今日だよ
The future continuing from that day is today we grabbed together!
もっともっともっと 加速するハート
More, more, more, my heart accelerates,
行くよどこまでも 準備はOK！
I'll go anywhere, preparation is OK!
キラメキ胸のトビラを 今すぐキラメキライダー☆
Open the sparkling door of your heart right now, Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's make the newborn excitement ring out!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me!
君に会いたくて やってきたんだ みんなで歌う 終わらないメロディ
I came here wanting to see you, an endless melody we sing together,
キラメキにのって
Riding on the brilliance!
全然怖くないよ 全然大丈夫だからみんな
I'm not scared at all, I'm totally fine, everyone!
ちょうど出せてたかな 私の声
Was I able to properly put out my voice?
届けたいのは 満面の笑顔
What I want to deliver is a beaming smile.
みんなどんな気分だったね ギュッとギュッとギュッと 胸を締め付けたきしめて
How did everyone feel? Squeezing my chest tight,
行くよどこまでも 準備はOK！ 進めキボウの道を 123でキラメキライダー☆
I'll go anywhere, preparation is OK! Advance on the path of hope!
すすめていこう この道を 123 キラメキライダー☆
Let's advance down this road, 1-2-3 Kirameki Rider☆
好きな気持ちを 順にかなえていんだ
Fulfilling our favorite feelings one by one,
最高の場所 最高の仲間と
With the best place and the best friends,
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's no illusion!
次の心が 幸せに染まるように 高めてくハモり キラメキライダー☆
Raising our harmony so our next hearts are dyed in happiness, Kirameki Rider☆
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな バカばっかまじめでいいじゃん
I want to keep singing, keep dancing, it's fine to be serious about being silly!
一緒にさあ キラメキライダー☆
Together now, Kirameki Rider☆
歌って楽しんできたことも 変わんない 輝くステージで 共に歩もう
The things we've enjoyed singing haven't changed, let's walk together on the shining stage!
ずっと一緒 キラメキライダー☆
Together forever, Kirameki Rider☆
はじめよう みんな！ 走ろう 3Dで！ ずっとよろしくね！
Let's start, everyone! Let's run in 3D! Thank you for everything always!
楽しいだけじゃ語れない 今も今もある悩みはあるけど
You can't talk about it with just fun, even now there are worries and troubles, but
ここにいるよ 私 ここにいるよ 君と同じ世界を見つめて
I'm right here, I'm right here, gazing at the same world as you,
キラメキライダー☆ 生まれたてのドキドキを 響かせよう
Kirameki Rider☆ Let's make the newborn excitement ring out!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me!
かつてきたんだ みんなで歌う 終わらないメロディ キラメキにのって
We came this far, an endless melody we sing together, riding on the brilliance!
キラメキ乗って キラメキもっと
Riding the sparkle, sparkling even more,
キラメキもっと乗ってるよ びりびり来てるよ！
Sparkling even more, it's coming through with tingles!
ありがとうみんな！ ありがとう！
Thank you everyone! Thank you!
電流を流しながらの試練でした！
That was a trial with electric currents!
みんなどうだった？
How was it, everyone?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
拍手もたくさんありがとう！
Thank you so much for the applause too!
なんかね、いまね、待ってやめてちょっと待って
Wait, hold on, right now... stop, wait a second.
このBGMがさ、あの、あの電流として来てんんだけどさ、
This BGM is, um, coming in like an electric current,
まあね、なんとね、はあとが叫んだら電流も、あの、反応してまた叫んだ音とともに電流がまた流れるというね、
well, you know, when Haato screams, the current responds and flows again along with the scream sound,
はあちゃんが、あの、電流が流れた時に叫んだとたんまたその電流もまた来るっていうね、なんというか、悪循環みたいな感じになってるんだけど、
so when Haato screams when the current flows, the current comes again instantly, it's like a vicious cycle,
あ、でもね、これでね、あの、電流と一緒にね、ライブをすることによってね、今年もね、最強アイドルとして頑張れるんじゃないかと思います！
ah, but, you know, by doing a live together with the current, I think this year too, as the strongest idol, I can do my best!
ありがとうスーパーチャットもありがとう、レベル10！
Thank you, thank you for the Super Chats too, Level 10!
ありがとう！来年はレベルマックスで挑めるように、もっと最強アイドルになれるように、がんばるから、
Thank you! I'll do my best so I can challenge it at Level Max next year and become an even stronger idol,
みんな応援よろしくね！
so everyone please support me!
おーー！
Ooh!
というわけで、まあね、電流の試練はね、終わったわけで、
So, well, the electric current trial is over,
え、このあとね、なんと実写ねゲストも呼んでおります！
and after this, amazingly, we've invited an actual guest!
はい、それではね、ま一度ね、今回はアイドル衣装をね、お披露目ということで、え、それに気合を入れるために、ちょっと部屋に行こうと思います！
Yes, so, well, once again, since we're debuting our idol outfits this time, to get hyped for that, I think I'll go to the room!
ということで、またね、またあとでね、ありがとう！じゃあね！
So, see you later, thank you! Bye-bye!
最近はやりのハーチャマクッキング 見た目はゴミでも中身は美味しい
Haachama cooking is all the rage lately, looks like trash inside it's delicious
最近はやりのハーチャマクッキング 友達に見せたら友達減る
Haachama cooking is all the rage lately, show it to friends and your friends decrease
50ハーチャマの強さが欲しいですか？
Do you want the strength of 50 Haachamas?
Haachama GRAND 50 栄養ドリンク
Haachama GRAND 50 Energy Drink
今、ハーチャマになることができます！ハーチャマクッキング好きになって、てとてとてと…
Now you can become Haachama! Fall in love with Haachama cooking, tetotetoteto...
てとてとてとてとてとてとてと…
tetotetoteto...
はーちゃまっちゃまー！みんなー！
Haachamatchama! Everyone!
アイドル衣装の、はーちゃまっちゃまだよー！
It's Haachamatchama in our idol outfits!
はーちゃまのアイドル衣装を見て、みんなも頭はーちゃまっちゃまになってねー！大きい感情！
Look at Haachama's idol outfit and everyone go totally Haachamatchama in your heads! Such big emotions!
よし、久しぶりの、3D配信！
Alright, it's been a while since our last 3D stream!
なんとね、電流で始まるとは思わなかったんだけどね！
You know, I didn't think it would start with electric current!
いやーちょっとね、今からね、アイドル衣装、そして、アイドル衣装といえば、だってなんかよく分かんないこと言ってたけど、
Man, um, from now on, our idol outfits... and speaking of idol outfits, well, I was saying some incomprehensible stuff, but
まあ、撮影会をね、していこうと思います！そしてね、ゲストを呼んでいるので、ちょっと呼びたいと思いまーす！
well, I think we're going to do a photo shoot! And since we've invited a guest, I'd like to call them out!
えー、ここ会長、カモン！
Um, Coco-kaichou, come on!
あ、カチコミじゃ！
Ah, a surprise attack!
やー！
Yay!
はーちゃま！アイドル衣装じゃ！
Haachama! It's an idol outfit!
行くよ、行くよ、行くよ！
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
どっちだよ、こっちだ！
Which way? This way!
近付け、近付け！
Get closer, get closer!
それかい、どっちだよ！
Is that it, which way?!
何だと思ったんだ！
What did you think it was?!
よし、ガキモータの何してんだよ、お前ら！
Alright, what are you guys doing, Gakimota!?
っていうことでね、え、今日はね、アイドル衣装を、え、ここ会長と一緒にちょっとね、撮影していこうと思いまーす！
So, um, today, we're going to take photos of our idol outfits together with Coco-kaichou!
撮影タイム！はい、せっかくだから！いいよ、いいよ、私も期待！
Photo shoot time! Yes, since we have the chance! Sure, sure, I'm looking forward to it too!
あれ、ていうか、あでもね、ここ会長は来たんだけど、なんかカメラマンがいないわね、ちょっとね、なんか
Oh, wait, Coco-kaichou came, but somehow there's no cameraman, you know, like...
誰かいないかな、カメラマンになってくれる…
Is there anyone who can be our cameraman...?
あっ、ごめんなさい！取り直す、取り直す！
Ah, sorry! Let's retake it, retake it!
あれ、なんだろう、のかな、のかな…
Huh, I wonder, I wonder...
え、今日はなんとかなたをね、カメラマンとして呼びました！
Uh, today we invited Kanata as our cameraman!
なんか、ポーズをね、やっぱりアイドルだから、アイドルとしてね、可愛いポーズで、ちょっと撮影してもらおうかと！おぉ！
Like, since she's an idol, we want her to take photos of us in cute idol poses! Oh!
なんかちょっと、うんうん、びっくりしたんだけどはーちゃま、あの、か、なに、あの
I was a bit surprised, Haato, like, um, what, that...
電気が流れてたの？そうなのさ！はーちゃま電流アイドルだから！
Were you running electricity? That's right! Haato is a current idol!
電流アイドルはーちゃま！嫌なの？いや、じゃねえ、そんな電流アイドルのはーちゃまとここにはね
Current idol Haato! Do you hate it? No, it's not that, with current idol Haato and Coco here,
あの、ちょっと、あの、カメラに寄っていただいて、ちょっと顔をね、アップ、アップで、にゃんにゃんポーズとかどう？にゃんにゃん！アップ、にゃんにゃん！
um, please get closer to the camera, and with your faces up close, how about Nyan-nyan poses? Nyan-nyan! Close-up, Nyan-nyan!
じゃあ行くよ！あ、かわいい！にゃんにゃん！にゃんにゃん！がん見がん見！
Then let's go! Ah, cute! Nyan-nyan! Nyan-nyan! Staring hard!
え、いっすね、いっすね！はい、これ、ポーズタイムな、すくしょ、みんな撮って、みんな撮って！あっ、目が見える、目が見える、前髪が見える、あ、かわいい！
Ah, nice, nice! Yes, this is pose time, screenshot, everyone take it, everyone take it! Ah, eyes are visible, eyes are visible, bangs are visible, ah, cute!
なんかかなたのことだから、ゴリラポーズか言うのかと思ったらかなた…
I thought since it's Kanata, she'd ask for a gorilla pose, but Kanata...
ゴリラポーズもお願いします！大迫力！すごい、すごい、すごい！腕力50ありそうなゴリラでお願いします！
Gorilla pose please too! So powerful! Amazing, amazing, amazing! Please do a gorilla that looks like it has 50 strength!
いいねいいね、結構、あの、ゴリラになに始めたの！
Good, good, pretty much, um, you started acting like a gorilla!
あ、今日のパンツ何色かなって確認しようとしたんだけど、あ、カメラ！
Ah, I was about to check what color my panties are today, but— ah, the camera!
パンツが見え！パンツが見え！
My panties are showing! My panties are showing!
あとでパンツはまだあるから、あとで、あとで！パンツ！
There are still more panties later, so later, later! Panties!
あの、2つ目は、Twitterとかでもね、使えるようななんか動画みたいなのがね、欲しいのね。
Um, second, I want something like a video that can be used on Twitter and stuff.
燃えたときとかさ、限界化したときとかに使えるやつがね、いいなと思うんだけど。
Something usable when things are burning or when reaching my limit, that'd be nice.
あ、ちょっと待って。この正面のカメラに向かってちょっと走っ、すごい顔で、驚いた顔とかで、あ、燃えた！やべえみたいなの、欲しい！
Ah, wait a minute. Running toward the front camera with a crazy face, like a surprised face— like 'Ah, it's burning! Oh crap!', I want that!
走ってきてくれ。なんか、あれ、あの、ガンギマリな顔ってこと？ガンギマリの顔で、走ってきてほしい。
Run over here. Is that a totally spaced-out face? With a spaced-out face, I want you to run over.
ガンギマリ。ガンギマリな顔、あ、びっくりがお、びっくりがお。
Spaced out. A spaced-out face— ah, a surprised face, a surprised face.
ガンギマリますか？ガンギマリますか？ガンギマリで走ってきてほしい。
Do you go spaced out? Do you? I want you to run over totally spaced out.
ガンギマリの…あ、待って、ハートのハートの…
Spaced out... Ah, wait, Heart's— Heart's—
ハートのハートが光ってる、かっこいいですか？
Heart's heart is glowing, is that cool?
ちょっと緊張してる？もしかして。ずっと、ずっとだね。えっと、あと、おどろきがお、あれ？
Are you nervous? Maybe. Always, always. Um, also, a surprised face, huh?
まだ流れてる、電気？あ、待って、あ、でも今も、ポーズ、パンツが見えた気がする！あ、見えなかったか。
Is the electricity still flowing? Ah, wait, but even now, I feel like my panties were visible! Ah, guess not.
ガンギマリを、赤井はあとじゃあ最後にやっぱりパンツタイムが必要ってことで、あの二人ともね、あの後ろを向いておしりフリフリのセクシーダンスをね、踊ってほしいなと、あ、これは…
As for the spaced out one, Akai Haato, well finally, since a panty time is necessary, turn around and do a butt-shaking sexy dance, I'd love for you to— ah, this is...
思います。セクシーダンス、だってできるんですか？天音アイドルが。
I think so. A sexy dance? Can you do that, Amane Idol?
あ、あら！わあ！あ、エロい。あ、いいねそのココの腰の動き。腰の動きを真似て、真似て、もっともっと、ちょっとローアングルいきますかね、これね、
Ah, my! Wow! Ah, lewd. Ah, I like Coco's hip movement. Imitate that hip movement, imitate, more and more, shall we go with a low angle for this?
ローアングルで撮っちゃっていいすかね？天音さん、いいすか？これ。ちょっともうちょい下から撮っちゃおうかな。
Is it okay to shoot from a low angle? Amane-san, is that okay? I might shoot from a bit lower.
エロいですか？これ。みんな、あ、やだ！見ちゃダメ！見ちゃダメ！パンツが見えた気がするんだろ！お、見えなかった。
Is this lewd? Everyone— ah, no! Don't look! Don't look! You feel like my panties were visible, right? Oh, wasn't visible.
最高。ありがとうございます。新年初のゼロライブ、ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます！
The best. Thank you very much. Thank you for the very first zero-live of the New Year. Thank you very much!
という感じでね、僕のターン、これで終わりかな？ありがとうございます。はあとちゃんありがとー！
And with that, I guess my turn is over? Thank you very much, Haato-chan!
ハートちゃん、ハートちゃん。ハートちゃんよ、なんでパンツ入ってんのこれ？
Haato-chan, Haato-chan. Haato-chan, hey, why are panties inside this?
パンツから入って、パンツ？ふざけんなよ。このモンスター、本当にこの先輩アイドルなんすかね？
Entering from panties, panties? Are you kidding me. Is this senior really an idol?
ワンになっちゃった。あ、ちょちょ、あれ、何してらっしゃるんですか？
Turned into a dog. Ah, wait, what are you doing?
確認してんのよ今日のパンツの状況を。タフさんが困ってるんですよ今あの皆さんに出すスケジュール聞きますと。
I'm checking the status of today's panties. Taff-san is troubled right now when asking about the schedule to give everyone.
よし、じゃあね、あれ？はい、次もまだまだね、あと二人で呼んでいるんで、次、誰が来るかな？
Alright, then, huh? Yes, next, since we're calling two more people, who's coming next?
誰ですか？おいで、おいで、おいで！おいで！今日のかわいい！天龍って。
Who is it? Come, come, come! Today's cute— Tenga!
大丈夫かよ。また今度一緒にやる？なんで？やばいね。
Are you okay? Shall we do it together next time? Why? That's crazy.
あ、星街はあとちゃん。星街すいせいです。すいちゃん、こんにちはー。
Ah, Hoshimachi Haato-chan. It's Hoshimachi Suisei. Suisei-chan, helloー.
じゃあなんか、えっと、なんかしてん、すいせいいって言う話なので、ぜひぜひ。
So, like, um, something 'do Suisei' is the topic, so, please, please.
まずはじゃあ、寝転がってもらってもいいですか？おっと？寝転がる、ふん。
First, then, could you lie down? Oh? Lie down.
はい、寝転がっ、はい、寝転がってください。はい。まな板の上で。
Yes, please lie down. Yes. On a cutting board.
はい。で、その膝を立ててください。はい。で、その膝を会長抑えてもらっていいですか、はあとまの膝。膝を抑える？
Yes. And, put your knees up. Please. And can you hold down those knees, Chairman, Haato-chan's knees. Hold the knees?
はい。じゃあはあとま、腹筋100回！おら！これシレンツ！
Yes. Then Haato-chan, 100 sit-ups! Take this! This is Silence—!
いや、待て待て、腹筋ってなんですか？
Wait, wait, wait, what are sit-ups?
確認してんのよ今日のパンツの状況を！がんばれはあとま！皆さんぜひこの…
I'm checking the status of today's panties! Do your best, Haato-chan! Everyone, please take lots of pictures!
汗のしたたるはあとまをたくさん撮ってください！汗のしたたるビショビショのはあとまをたくさん撮ってください！はあとま、マックスですね。いい匂いがいんてきました。
Take lots of pictures of dripping, soaked Haato-chan! Haato-chan, max. A nice smell has come out.
はあとま、もういいですか？結構、やってくれましたよ。すごい！さすが天竜アイドル！
Haato-chan, is that enough? You've done quite a lot. Amazing! As expected of the Tenryū idol!
コクが違うぜ。ここが電流アイドルですよ。はあとま、いつか絶対やり返してやるからな！
The depth is different. This is the current idol. Haato-chan, I'll definitely pay you back someday!
たくさん屈伸したところに、じゃあ次は
Since we've done a lot of squats, next up,
ブリッジをしてください。
please do a bridge.
うわあ、ブリッジ！
Whoa, a bridge!
なんか今日ね、あの運営さんに、あれブリッジって禁止になったんですかって聞いたら、
I asked management today if bridges were banned, and...
あれ、あ、みたいなただただ、
they were like, "Huh? Oh..."
なんか、なんこう、ね、あのー、ちょっとね、なんかブリッジしちゃうみたいな感じでいけば
and if we go about it like doing a bridge or something...
おっ、おっ、おっ、あーっ！
Oh, oh, oh, ah!
あー、簡単！
Ah, easy!
ちょっと、あの、あのハートのは、あの、危ないです。
Wait, Haato's is, um, pretty dangerous.
禁止にした理由が分かりましたね。
I understand why it was banned.
皆さんブリッジは止めましょう。
Everyone, let's stop doing bridges.
いや、まっ、ハートがね、今ね、あの怒られてるんです、スタッフにね、あの、ちょっと私で、私の可愛さで
Well, Haato is getting scolded by the staff right now, so with my cuteness...
会長の指示をください！
Please give me your instructions, Kaichou!
あ、わたしの頭がガクガクです。
Ah, my head is shaking so much.
まだありました。
There's still more.
はあちゃま、ブリッジはやはりあれだったんですね。
Haachama, bridges really were that way, huh?
そうですね、危なかったですね。おっ、ブリッジ？
That's right, it was dangerous. Oh, a bridge?
おっ、できます？私最近ますけど。おっ、おっ、
Oh, can you do it? I can do it recently too. Oh, oh—
え、できる？できる？ブリッジいける？
Eh, can you? Can you? Can you do a bridge?
ちょっとね、あの全力で今やめろって怒られて
I was told with full force to stop right now,
やめますけどね、ブリッジはだめだったな。
so I'll stop, but bridges were no good.
じゃあ次は、腹筋横跳びしてもらおうかな。
Next up, let's have her do abdominal side jumps.
腹筋横跳び？いいよ。
Abdominal side jumps? Sure.
やるぞ！はい！えい！えい！おー！
Let's do it! Yeah! Hey! Hey! Oh!
よし！いいぞ！
Alright! Looking good!
はあちゃまも！がんばれ！
Haachama too! Do your best!
がんばれはあちゃまも！がんばれ！
Hang in there, Haachama! Do your best!
よしよしよし、光ってる、輝いてる。
Good, good, good, she's glowing, she's shining!
あ、もう無理になってしまいました。
Ah, I've reached my limit.
はあちゃま！はあちゃまがんばってるなあ。
Haachama! Haachama is working hard.
すいちゃん！
Suisei!
はあちゃまがね、今年こそ最強のアイドルとなると言っておりますから、体力づくりは大事ですよね。
Haachama says she'll become the strongest idol this year, so building stamina is important, right?
確かにね。そうだなったら、なるほどね。そうなんです。
That's true. If so, I see. Exactly.
もうそんなね、汗もしたたるはあちゃまをね、写真撮って来たらいいなと思いまして、皆さん撮れましたか？
So I thought it'd be nice to take pictures of dripping-with-sweat Haachama. Everyone, were you able to take some?
これ完璧ですか？
Is this perfection?
どう、どうなのこれ？これいい、いいえ撮れたかな、みんな？
How is this? Did everyone get a good picture?
いいえ撮れたかな、みんな？撮れました？きっとね、GIFになってTwitter上で流行りますよ。
Did you get one, everyone? I'm sure it'll become a GIF and trend on Twitter.
GIF、GIFは、はあちゃま反復横跳び
A GIF? Haachama's side-to-side jumps—
あ、すいちゃんありがとう！
Ah, thank you, Suisei!
ありがとう、はあちゃま、また一緒に遊ぼうね！ありがとう今日来てくれて。ありがとう、体力づくりもがんばってね！ありがとう！バイバーイ！
Thank you, Haachama, let's play together again! Thanks for coming today. Thank you, keep working hard on stamina! Thank you! Bye-bye!
またやりますか？まだね、体力があとね、ちょっとやるためにあとでダンスするから残しとかないと。
Shall we do it again? We still need stamina because we'll be dancing later, so we have to save some.
そうだよ、体力残しとかないと。おっ、そしたら最後かな？
That's right, we gotta save our stamina. Oh, is that the last one?
最後にもう一人。やあ！やあ！やあ！わっしょい！
One more person at the end. Yay! Yay! Yay! Wasshoi!
この子ね！わためちゃんが来たよ！
It's this girl! Watame-chan is here!
わため、お邪魔します！
Watame, pardon the interruption!
わためちゃんが来たよ！わためちゃん、どのポーズさせるの？
Watame-chan is here! Watame-chan, what pose are you going to make her do?
まず、はあちゃまの右、右腕をちょっと上げてもらって。
First, have Haachama raise her right arm a bit—
脇脇か？
Armpit pose?
おっ、おっ、いいね！
Oh, oh, nice!
で、ちょっと会長のほぐちに、あ、ほぐち、あ、動いてあったん。
And, to Kaichou's... armpit— ah, it moved.
ほぐちは、わための代わりにちょっと、あ、脇、脇ペロとか、
For the armpit, instead of Watame, like licking the armpit—
脇ペロダメ！
Armpit licking is no good!
脇ペロNGなのだ！NGに決まってんだろ！わためちゃん、別にいいんだけどね、運営さんが許さないかなと思って。
Armpit licking is NG! Of course it's NG! Watame-chan, it's fine by me, but I thought management wouldn't allow it.
わためだったら言ってるけどね。わためでも許されないよ！
If it were Watame, she'd say it. Even Watame wouldn't be allowed!
運営さんがちょっとYouTubeくんが許さないからちょっと。
Management— YouTube-kun won't allow it, so...
YouTubeくんが許さないから。脇ペロまずいよ、そんなプレーはまずいよ。
YouTube-kun won't allow it. Armpit licking is bad, that kind of play is bad.
じゃあ次に、わため今端っこにいるんだけど、これ真ん中に寄せてもらうことってできる？
Next, Watame is at the edge right now, can we have her move to the center?
まん中、はじっこにしますか？
Center, or keep her at the edge?
じゃあ、わためとほぐちのパイで、ちょっと挟んでもらって。アップで、アップで、あの挟んでもらって真ん中に！
Then, let's sandwich her between Watame and Kaichou's boobs. In close-up, sandwich her in the center!
にににに、待ってやばい、わためやばい、わためやばい、やばいやばい、わためちょっと待って、待って！
Wait, oh no, Watame is in trouble, Watame, no, no, wait, wait!
スタッフの怒りです！
That's the staff's wrath!
あ、ダメメタ。あのエネルギー出ました。
Ah, it hit the limit. That energy came out.
取れたか?
Did you get it?
目のとこ自分に置き換えて使いますよ、これ。
You replace the eye part with yourself and use it.
何に使うか知らんけど。
I don't know what to use it for though.
何に使うって何だよ、わたメ!
What do you mean "what to use it for", Watame!
胸枕にしてよ！
Use it as a chest pillow!
胸枕にしていいよ、さらさらだよ。
You can use it as a chest pillow, it's smooth!
お尻を、あ、胸枕にしていいよ。
Use your butt-- oh, as a chest pillow.
や、強制的に、あ、あ、おじさんパイス
Wait, forcibly-- oh, oh, uncle's high-piled...
おじさんさようなら、またおじさんさようなら！
Goodbye, uncle! Goodbye again, uncle!
寂しい！またおじさんさようなら！
So lonely! Goodbye again, uncle!
でも、まだやってもいいってことだよ、これ。
But that means we can still keep going, right?
またおじさん、またおじさん...
Another uncle, another uncle...
ラスト1個。うんうん。
Last one. Yep, yep.
え、1個?
Eh, one more?
じゃあ、高速で行こう、じゃあ。
Then let's go at high speed.
ステップにやってほしい。じゃあまず、はぁちゃまが四つんばいで、
I want you to do it in steps. First, Haato on all fours,
四つんばいは、赤は、赤わのカメラの、あ、赤わカメラの方ね。うん。
All fours-- wait, Haato camera side. Yeah.
で、会長は、あの、お尻をちょっとね、踏んでもいいんだけど、
And Coco, you can kind of step on her butt, but...
あ、ちょっと足を乗せる。
Ah, just put your foot on it.
おい！そんなことできるか! 三敗だぞ!
Hey! Can you do that?! That's three defeats!
そんなことできるか! これは特殊な壁に刺さると思うんだが...
Can you do that?! I think this is like getting stuck in a special wall...
まずいよ、こんなの！
This is bad, something like this!
お尻が挟まって...
My butt is stuck...
逆は? 逆は? 逆は?
What about the reverse? Reverse?
なるほど。こう違う。四つんばいは...
I see. It's different like this. All fours is...
ほらほらほら！ めったに巡り会えよ、会長のこんな...
Look, look, look! You rarely encounter Coco like this...
やばい！尻尾が...
Oh no! My tail...
めったに見れないとこ見れちゃうよ！うれぇあ！うれぇあ！
You can see things you rarely get to see! Ugh-ah! Ugh-ah!
なんか、尻尾がなんか挟まって... 尻尾がなんかあれだけど...
Somehow, my tail is stuck... The tail is kind of...
やばい、やばい、いいい...
Oh no, oh no, ii...
尻尾が... 尻尾がちょっと... よし。あ、危ない危ない。
The tail... the tail is a bit... Okay. Ah, that was close.
一気に... すれすれだったね。
All at once... That was close.
もうおじさん満足しちゃった...
Uncle is already satisfied...
おじさん帰ってください！
Uncle, please go home!
またおじさん満足しちゃった。
Uncle got satisfied again.
ありがとね！
Thank you!
またやろうね！ありがとね！バイバイ！
Let's do it again! Thank you! Bye-bye!
よし、これでバッチリ写真撮れたんじゃないの? 今のめちゃくちゃ撮れたと...
Alright, didn't we take a great photo with this? The photo we just took was amazing...
いい感じ? みんなね、大事にね、スクショ撮ってもらって。
Looks good? Everyone, please cherish it and take a screenshot.
まあね、アイドル衣装に着替えたってことはさ、やっぱりね、やることは一つよね。
Well, changing into idol outfits means, after all, there's only one thing to do.
私たち、このライブ、イングリッシュで、歌っちゃおうと！歌っちゃいます！すごーい！
We're going to sing this live in English! We're gonna sing it! Awesome!
そしてね、今回のテーマは、え、ダンス、セクシーダンスをね、二人で。
And the theme this time is, uh, dance, a sexy dance, the two of us.
じゃあここ、ここ会長、直前でのね、セクシーダンスで二人でね、踊りながら歌いながら、やっていきたいと思います。
So Coco, Coco-kaichou, right before, let's do a sexy dance together while dancing and singing.
行くよー! チェンジ、チェンジ、チェンジ、ドラ!
Here we go! Change, change, change, dra!
はぁちゃま はぁちゃま
Haachama, Haachama
チャンネル登録してよ
Subscribe to the channel
いついつ 見るの
When will you watch?
毎秒動画見てね
Watch every second of the video
正気な狂気のコンテンツ
Insane crazy content
後ろのはぁちゃまだあれ
Haachama is just behind you
はぁちゃま はぁちゃま
Haachama, Haachama
チャンネル登録してる?
Are you subscribed to my channel?
いまいま見てよ
Watch me right now
毎秒思い出すのよ
You won't forget me
精神のトリップしたいよね
You want to become crazy?
後ろのはぁちゃまだあれ
I'm always behind you
同じ未来を見ていたい あの夢手に行きたい
We took our hands towards the brightest screens
それぞれ違った ココロで走れGO
All we wish are shining dreams
どこを見ても真っ暗な 場所に芽生えてた
We make our choice with different voice
ほんの小さな希望に この瞳奪われた
Oh yes we know get set and GO!
セクシー セクシー セクシー ダンス?
Sexy sexy sexy dance?
セクシー デハナ イ?
Sexy is that right?
君の笑顔は 保存して 進む
You were the one who set this light of smile
It was a dark and hopeless place
It was your shiny eyes that caught me
Filled with hope, this story starts now
Notice the fear inside me bouncing up?
That's when I tune my heart beat down
I will shine, I will smile, my wish will come true
The first page of my history
Voice telling me to "give it up"
Delete that word my head's up
I will never be alone, no, not anymore
We are the shiny, smiley star!
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Giving all, we are now a team!
I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!
Let's show this world, our dreamland!
Access through my heart, you will see
No regrets with hottest degree
We make our choice with different voice
Oh yes we know get set and go!
Glow to the top of my sky above
My precious shiny, smiley days
It's a light you have never seen before
Sending for you, c'mon and get it!
Do you remember all the love that you gave?
It's all here with me, I saved
Every voice, every word I get from you...
But not enough, I want it more
Your precious smile is like a spell
A magic dust that makes me smile
You'll never see my tears, we defeat despairs
'Cause it's my shiny, smiley life!
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Wonder story, ready to scream?
Together we can make it free
A never ending story
Everyone's a star in this tale
Filled with love and shine and a smile
We made our choice with different voice
Oh, yes we know get set and burst!
When I'm sad, you'll be here
When you're torn, I'll be there
Touch my screen and you will feel my heart here
Whenever you're near, there would be no fear
This beat will dry out every tears
Look at my future, shine and glow
Make every world to know
My shiny smile!
We took our hands towards our brightest stage
This is me, in my shiny page
Tear of joy and gold happy days
Just a start that we had just made
Hold my hands to see our "mirai"
Please my dreams come true for my life
Let the legend start, step by step a miracle
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Giving all, we are now a team!
I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!
Let's show this world, our dream come true!
Access through my heart, you will see
No regrets, my heart is now free
We make our choices with different voices
Oh yes, we will create our world
というわけで、ここからちょうど二人で「Shiny Smily Story」でしたー！
And with that, right from here, the two of us performed "Shiny Smily Story"!
ありがと、はあちゃま！ありがとう！
Thank you, Haachama! Thank you!
またね！ありがとうございましたー！
See you! Thank you very much!
はい！ということで、本当に最高だった！ありがとう！
Yes! So, that was truly amazing! Thank you!
えー、それでは残すところあと一曲。
Uh, well, there's just one song left.
やっぱりね、最後はこの曲で締めたいと思います。
As expected, I'd like to close with this song.
それでは、次の曲いくよ！
Well then, let's go to the next song!
Hi, how are you?
Are you calling up my phone?
Baby tell me what is wrong
Don't you ever let me go
one, two, three, go!
hi, how are you?
are you calling up my phone?
baby tell me what is wrong
don't you ever let me go
hi, i am good
i am still looking for proof
am i good enough for you?
don't you tell me what's my rule
this is me, are you coming on the ride
we're going super high
got to be who what i like
you and me, are you ready for the fight?
alright, alright, alright
stronger than i've ever been before
this is who i am
nothing in the way
today and far away
you and me
we make the part of me
i give you my big red heart
my, my big red heart
i'll be true to my big red heart
hi! over there
thank you for coming along
on this journey of my own
promise me you won't let go
yes, this is me
i am falling but i'm strong
'cause you got me in your arms
don't you ever let me go
i want you to come with me on the ride
this is going super high
i am falling from the sky
got to be who you wanna be, that's right
alright, alright, alright, let's go!
i am still a girl
figuring out what's true or false
in this whole wide world
i'm your only girl
tell me once more what's really going on with you
i'm looking for the right one on the road
the one that'll always take me back to you
this can be home, will you be my home?
stronger than i ever been before
this is who i am
nothing in the way
today and far away
you and me
we make the part of me
i give you my big red heart
my, my big red heart
i'll be true to my big red heart
田舎、川楽しんでくれたかな？
Did you enjoy the countryside and river?
みんな、頭はっちゃめちゃになれた？
Everyone, were you able to go totally crazy?
i give you my big red heart
my, my big red heart
i'll be true to my big red heart
はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Haachama-chama!
i'm the single girl
figuring out what's true or false
in this whole wide world
i'm the only girl
figuring out what's my world
going on video
i'm looking for the right one on the road
the one that'll always take me back to you
this can be home, will you be my home?
stronger than i've ever been before
this is who i am
nothing in the way
today and far away
you and me
we make the part of me
i give you my big red heart
my, my big red heart
i'll be true to my big red heart
my red heart!
mama red heart!
arigato!
haachama-chama!
赤井はあと Haato Channel
[Title: Haato Channel]
Subscribe to my channel
Follow my Twitter @akaihaato
[Follow my Twitter]
Click the like button
SEE YOU NEXT STREAM